dramacityhiphop.com 2017-10-02

# Privacy Policy DRAMACITYHIPHOP

Last modified July 1, 2011

The privacy of visitors to this site is very important to us. This Privacy Policy gives you information on what types of personal information we collect when you use this site, and our practices with respect to the use and disclose of such information.  By visiting hiphop-1971194775.us-east-1.elb.amazonaws.com collectively DCITY you agree to this Privacy Policy and to the Terms of Service (TOS) which is located [HERE](http://localhost/dramacityhiphop/videos/terms.php).

## Information You Give Us:

We receive and may store any personal information you enter on our Website or may give us in any other way. This information may include your name or email address, content you submit to the website,  
and other information.

## Information We Automatically Collect:

We may automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, DCITY allows guest commenting. When you make a guest comment, we may publish the content of your comment and may collect your IP (internet protocol) address, the time and the date you made the comment. We do not use cookies to collect or store information about you.

## How We Use Information About You:

We may use the information that you provide for a variety of purposes, including to respond to your requests, to improve the overall quality of the Website, and to communicate with you, among other things.

When we disclose information about you:

We never disclose your personal information to third parties.

For information you give us, or information we automatically collect, certain records may be produced to law enforcement or private litigants in response to valid legal process. DCITY reserves the right to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We reserve the right to disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement  
officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of DCITY or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable.

DCITY also reserves the right to, but is not obligated to, refuse to disclose confidential sources or unpublished information we collect as part of our journalistic and/or newsgathering and reporting  
under federal and/or state law.
